(Raj:)Lucy?
(Lucy:)Hey, long time no see.
(Raj:)You don't know me very well,
but each time you crawl out a window...
(Raj:)...to escape my company,
it chips away at my masculinity.
(Raj:)- I'm sorry.
- Why would you leave like that?
(Lucy:)You were pushing me.
I didn't want to send my food back...
(Lucy:)...and you tried to make me do it.
(Raj:)If I upset you,
why didn't you say something?
(Lucy:)How can I tell you I'm upset
if I can't tell the woman at Supercuts...
(Lucy:)...that my forehead's my best feature?
(Lucy:)- It's scary.
- Well, I like you a lot and that's scary for me.
(Raj:)Mostly because you're a proven flight risk.
(Lucy:)How could you like me a lot?
Well... For one thing, you have
bigger emotional problems than I do...
(Raj:)...and I find that very attractive in a woman.
(Raj:)I don't know, I just...